cloudera.com 2019-06-30

# Cloudera's Privacy and Data Policies

### About Cloudera and This Policy

Cloudera, Inc. is the controller of data collected on or through this Web site and of contact and billing information of our business customers. You can contact our Data Protection Officer at [privacy@cloudera.com](mailto:privacy@cloudera.com).

More

### Data Hosting and Privacy Shield

Cloudera is a global company and may host or access your personal data in multiple countries, including in the United States. To help protect your data and allow for data transfer from the European Union to the United States, Cloudera participates in the U.S. Privacy Shield program.

More

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Cloudera may change this privacy policy from time to time. The date at the top of the Privacy Policy will indicate how recently we have done so. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy.

More

### Information Collection

We may collect information directly from you, public sources, third parties, such as your name and contact information when you create an account, interact with us about our Services, apply for a job through our career site, or buy our products, through an order form or otherwise. We may also automatically collect some information about you when you use our Services, such as information resulting from your visit to our Web site and information about the browser and device you use. We may use cookies and other tracking technologies, though you may change your browser preferences in order to control the cookies we set. 

More

### More About the Information We Collect

With your consent, we may allow you to publicly post blogs, community forum discussions, and testimonials. You can request removal from any of these public postings.

If you interact with a social media feature, the third party powering the feature may receive some of your personal data, such as your IP address. If you apply for a job by signing into the job application service through LinkedIn or other social media, that social media provider may receive some of your personal data, such as your name and email address, to assist you in completing our job application form. You can also use social media single sign-on capability to publicly post information about your activities with us.

More

### Links to Third Party Websites

Note that our website may link to third party websites over whose privacy practices we have no control. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of these third parties before submitting to them your personal data. If you receive marketing from these third parties and wish to stop receiving marketing messages, please contact these third parties directly.

### Use of Information

We may use your personal data to provide and improve our Services and products, respond to your requests, process payments on your account, bill you for products or services purchased by you, communicate with you about your Service, monitor trends associated with our Service, and communicate with you about contest entries and rewards. We may also request your input through surveys. We use personal data to help keep data safe and prevent fraud. If you apply for a job with us, we will use the information you provide to consider your application and communicate with you. With your consent we may communicate with you about our products and services. Contact us to object to our processing or withdraw your consent.

More

### Sharing of Information

We may share your personal data with:

  * Our subprocessors under contract to us (see our current list of subprocessors),

  * Third parties such as auditors, outside counsel or regulatory agencies in order to comply with legal obligations and protect our legal interests,

  * Third parties in cases of merger, sale, or acquisition,

  * Cloudera commercial partners,

  * Third parties for other purposes, with your consent.

Note that our website uses frames that may provide content to third parties, in which case the privacy policies of these third parties apply. We also allow third party advertisements on our website. These third parties may receive some information about you and your website behavior, though you can choose to not allow us to provide this information.

More

### Security

We take reasonable technical, procedural, and administrative security measures to help protect your personal data. You can contact us with questions about the security of your data, and we encourage you to take measures to protect yourself, such as protecting your passwords. Visit our Security and Compliance page for additional information.

More

### Data Retention

We retain your personal data as long as required for our business purposes and legal obligations, according to our data retention policy.

More

### Your Rights and Information Choices

You can opt out of marketing materials and newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any marketing email, or submit a request at unsubscribe.

You can also ask us questions about privacy matters or request that we delete, correct, or provide you access to your personal data. You may have the right to request that we stop processing your data or limit our uses or sharing of your data. If you provided us consent to process your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent. Please contact us with any privacy questions or complaints. You may also have the right to address your concerns to a regulator.

More

### Use of this Website and Children

We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 16.

More

### Your California Privacy Rights

If you reside in California, USA, you may have the right to request information about how your personal data is shared with third parties. Contact us at [privacy@cloudera.com](mailto:privacy@cloudera.com) for more details.

More

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the information below:

Cloudera, Inc.  
395 Page Mill Rd  
Palo Alto, CA 94306

1-888-789-1488

Unsubscribe at: unsubscribe

More

### Information Related to Data Collected Through Our Services

When our Clients contract with us to provide service, we work at the direction of our Clients as a processor. This means that our Clients dictate how we use these data, how long to retain these data, and whether and how we assist with any data-related requests. If you are an end user customer of one of our Clients and have a privacy-related request or question, please contact that organization. We will assist our Clients fulfill your request at their instruction.

More

### Data Policy

Cloudera collects information that a Customer or other data sources may provide while using Cloudera’s Products and Services. We understand and respect the sensitive nature of the data you provide us and promise to maintain commercially reasonable administrative, physical and technical safeguards designed for the protection, confidentiality and integrity of the data. Our Data Policy details how we handle and store Cloudera’s customer data and addresses this data in three categories: “Transaction Data”, “Account Data”, and “Personal Data”.

More
